I have cash to burn.
Nobody can touch me.
Ted! Back to your
sideline now.
Good job.
Got your cash later
by the way.
You're talented.
Big fucking deal.
One word from me,
Henry gets you fired for leaking my plays.
The world belongs to people like us.
Nice little sweater
by the way.
Good look.
Crawling back,
I think she's calling you.
Let's go.
Eagles! Fight!
Fight! Fight!
The Eagles have taken the lead swiftly,
and there's only ten minutes left on the clock.
Looks as though
the Knights
might not pull off the miracle today.
Three of our key players are out.
If this keeps up,
we're finished.
West obviously
bribed the refs.
Unless we can
find someone
who's good enough to dodge hits and score,
we're done for.
Come on, coach, somebody like that
is top-tier at least.
We're in the middle of a damn game.
How are we supposed to find someone like that?
Alright, Ted, warm up.
Only you can save the Knights now.